<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Active Directory on Welcome to Andy Blog</title>
    <link>https://AndyLeeGT.github.io/tags/active-directory/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Active Directory on Welcome to Andy Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://AndyLeeGT.github.io/tags/active-directory/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Active Directory: Group and ShareFolder</title>
      <link>https://AndyLeeGT.github.io/active-directory-group-and-sharefolder/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://AndyLeeGT.github.io/active-directory-group-and-sharefolder/</guid>
      <description>Welcome back to the post again! In this post, we will talk about creating and adding group members, and explore the shared folder features.&#xA;Adding New Group One powerful method for organizing the users is by incorporating Group Organizational Units (OUs). These OUs offer a structured approach to managing groups within your network, providing enhanced organization and control over permissions and policies.&#xA;To get started, follow these steps below:&#xA;Access Active Directory Users and Computers: Launch the Active Directory Users and Computers (ADUC) console.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Active Directory: Configuration and Set up</title>
      <link>https://AndyLeeGT.github.io/active-directory-configuration-and-set-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://AndyLeeGT.github.io/active-directory-configuration-and-set-up/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Thank you for visiting my blog once again. In this post, we will discuss the setup of Active Directory, DHCP configuration, and account setup. It&amp;rsquo;s important to note that this setup drew significant inspiration from Josh Madakor&amp;rsquo;s HomeLab tutorial, which you can find at using belwo link:&#xA;&amp;ldquo;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=MHsI8hJmggI&amp;amp;t=1904s&amp;quot;.&#xA;laboratory Network Setup Let&amp;rsquo;s start by exploring the HomeLab setup. Our HomeLab utilizes Oracle VM VirtualBox to host virtual machines, including Windows 10 for client-side computers and Server 2019 for server hosting.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
